[
  {
    "question": "true",
    "answer": "bool"
  },
  {
    "question": "false",
    "answer": "bool"
  },
  {
    "question": "{0 ,3 ,8 ,2 ,0}",
    "answer": "set"
  },
  {
    "question": "{\"key_0\": 6, \"key_1\": 5, \"key_2\": 4}",
    "answer": "dict"
  },
  {
    "question": "{7 ,9 ,4}",
    "answer": "set"
  },
  {
    "question": "[7]",
    "answer": "list"
  },
  {
    "question": "16",
    "answer": "int"
  },
  {
    "question": "false",
    "answer": "bool"
  },
  {
    "question": "\"fdg\"",
    "answer": "str"
  },
  {
    "question": "true",
    "answer": "bool"
  },
  {
    "question": "[9, 3]",
    "answer": "list"
  },
  {
    "question": "{2 ,0}",
    "answer": "set"
  },
  {
    "question": "60.35",
    "answer": "float"
  },
  {
    "question": "54",
    "answer": "int"
  },
  {
    "question": "[9]",
    "answer": "list"
  },
  {
    "question": "-13.46",
    "answer": "float"
  },
  {
    "question": "-16",
    "answer": "int"
  },
  {
    "question": "-52",
    "answer": "int"
  },
  {
    "question": "[10, 9, 4, 10]",
    "answer": "list"
  },
  {
    "question": "{2 ,9}",
    "answer": "set"
  },
  {
    "question": "false",
    "answer": "bool"
  },
  {
    "question": "{\"key_0\": 3, \"key_1\": 2, \"key_2\": 7}",
    "answer": "dict"
  },
  {
    "question": "(8)",
    "answer": "tuple"
  },
  {
    "question": "\"irk\"",
    "answer": "str"
  },
  {
    "question": "{10}",
    "answer": "set"
  },
  {
    "question": "true",
    "answer": "bool"
  },
  {
    "question": "\"uohxrnyt\"",
    "answer": "str"
  },
  {
    "question": "{\"key_0\": 5, \"key_1\": 0, \"key_2\": 2}",
    "answer": "dict"
  },
  {
    "question": "true",
    "answer": "bool"
  },
  {
    "question": "\"xttctem\"",
    "answer": "str"
  },
  {
    "question": "-75.90",
    "answer": "float"
  },
  {
    "question": "(0, 7, 0)",
    "answer": "tuple"
  },
  {
    "question": "{8 ,0 ,3 ,10 ,6}",
    "answer": "set"
  },
  {
    "question": "{9 ,5 ,7 ,6}",
    "answer": "set"
  },
  {
    "question": "false",
    "answer": "bool"
  },
  {
    "question": "false",
    "answer": "bool"
  },
  {
    "question": "{4 ,3 ,1 ,7 ,3}",
    "answer": "set"
  },
  {
    "question": "{\"key_0\": 3}",
    "answer": "dict"
  },
  {
    "question": "-33",
    "answer": "int"
  },
  {
    "question": "false",
    "answer": "bool"
  },
  {
    "question": "-84.57",
    "answer": "float"
  },
  {
    "question": "{\"key_0\": 3, \"key_1\": 1}",
    "answer": "dict"
  },
  {
    "question": "(8, 8, 4, 0)",
    "answer": "tuple"
  },
  {
    "question": "(5, 5, 5, 4, 2)",
    "answer": "tuple"
  },
  {
    "question": "32.67",
    "answer": "float"
  },
  {
    "question": "\"okdojbo\"",
    "answer": "str"
  },
  {
    "question": "\"egyn musb\"",
    "answer": "str"
  },
  {
    "question": "{\"key_0\": 5, \"key_1\": 1}",
    "answer": "dict"
  },
  {
    "question": "[1, 1, 9]",
    "answer": "list"
  },
  {
    "question": "{1}",
    "answer": "set"
  }
]
